{
  "Questions":[
    {
      "id": 1,	
      "Question": "How many moons does Mars have?",
	    "Answers": [ "none", "1",  "2"],
      "Answer": 2,	
      "details": "Mars has 2 moons. They are named Phobos, meaning fear and Deimos, which is greek for panik."
    },
    {
      "id": 2,	
      "Question": "What is Marsâ€™s nickname?",
	    "Answers": [ "The red Planet", "The dusty planet", "The stinky planet" ],
      "Answer": 0,	
      "details": "Rusted iron particles in rocks give mars it's distinct red hue"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,	
      "Question": "About how long would it take to travel to Mars? ",
	    "Answers": [ "Three days", "One week",  "Eight months"],
      "Answer": 2,	
      "details": "Earth and Mars follow different orbits around the Sun, so space explorers must wait until the two planets are close together to blast off.Even then, the trip would take a minimum of about eight months."
    },
    {
      "id": 4,	
      "Question": "True or false? Scientists have found evidence of liquid water on Mars. ",
	    "Answers": [ "true", "false"],
      "Answer": 0,	
      "details": "Scientist think Mars once had rivers, lakes and maybe even oceans. Today small amounts of water trickle down crater walls"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,	
      "Question":"This planet is named after the Roman god Mars. What is he the god of? ",
	    "Answers": [ "Hunting", "War",  "Love"],
      "Answer": 1,	
      "details": "Ancient people (greeks? romans? inkas?... who ?) thought the planet looked as red as blood and named it after the roman god of war"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,	
      "Question": "question ",
	    "Answers": [ "", "",  ""],
      "Answer": 0,	
      "details": "answer"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "Question": "question ",
      "Answers": ["", "", ""],
      "Answer": 0,
      "details": "answer"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "Question": "question ",
      "Answers": ["", "", ""],
      "Answer": 0,
      "details": "answer"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "Question": "question ",
      "Answers": ["", "", ""],
      "Answer": 0,
      "details": "answer"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "Question": "question ",
      "Answers": ["", "", ""],
      "Answer": 0,
      "details": "answer"
    }    
  ]
}

